http://www.sayeghlaw.com/privacy-policy

HomeAboutAreas of PracticeAttorney BiosTestmonialsNewsPaymentsContactMENUPrivacy PolicyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Sayegh Law The Law Firm of William G. Sayegh, P.C. and our website; http://www.sayeghlaw.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:What information we collect;With whom it is shared;How it can be corrected;How it is secured;How policy changes will be communicated; andHow to address concerns over misuse of personal data. Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this website. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your dataOrders and Donations We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us or donate to us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and/or to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.Sharing We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.And/or: We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.And/or: We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Cookies We use "cookies" on this website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a website visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our website and identify repeat visitors to our website. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our website. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our website.Links This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information.Notification of ChangesThe Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time.  We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our website. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the website and this privacy page for updates.Contact UsIf you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Website, please contact us at (845) 228-4200.Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on February 13, 2018.(845) 228-420065 Gleneida AveCarmel, New YorkPrior results cannot and do not guarantee or predict a similar outcome with respect to any future matter, including yours, in which a lawyer or law firm may be retained.Terms and ConditionsPrivacy Policy© Sayegh Law 2017. All Rights Reserved. The Law Firm of William G. Sayegh, P.C.Designed by PMI Pros
